This is John and in this clip we will be identifying our problems.
Now there's a couple problems with our storm door.
Fist off, it is not a very high quality storm door.
It's made of weak materials and it's not very insulated.
Additionally, the home owner wants a white storm door with the nickel colored hardware.
Now our main entry door also does not have an insulation value that we would like.
So we're going to be replacing that with a better insulated door.
Now on the inside of our door, when the door is shut we can see light through it and that is not a good sign.
Additionally, the trim was damaged at some point, so we're going to be replacing that also.
Now additionally, there is a significant amount of air that leaks through the door on the bottoms, on the sides and on the top.
So by installing a new door, we're hoping to fix our air leak.
Now lastly, with a storm door, our storm door that we're going to be purchasing will have a screen in it where as this one does not.
That's going to really help the air circulation inside the house.